[
   {
      "Category":"SCIENCE",
      "Question":"I am a big liver, This organ removes excess glucose from the blood & stores it as glycogen",
      "Answer":"Liver",
      "Age":1
   },
   {
      "Category":"ANIMALS",
      "Question":"I am a big animal, It's the only living mammal in the order Proboseidea",
      "Answer":"Elephant",
      "Age":12
   },
   {
      "Category":"ANIMALS",
      "Question":"I am a big liver, The gavial looks very much like a crocodile except for this bodily feature",
      "Answer":"the nose or snout",
      "Age":12
   },
   {
      "Category":"ANIMALS",
      "Question":"I am a big liver, Weighing around a ton, the eland is the largest species of this animal in Africa",
      "Answer":"Antelope",
      "Age":1
   },
   {
      "Category":"ANIMALS",
      "Question":"I am a big liver, Heaviest of all poisonous snakes is this North American rattlesnake",
      "Answer":"the diamondback rattler",
      "Age":23
   },
   {
      "Category":"SCIENCE",
      "Question":"I am a big liver, 2000 news: the Gunnison sage grouse isn't just another northern sage grouse, but a new one of this classification",
      "Answer":"species",
      "Age":41
   },
   {
      "Category":"SCIENCE",
      "Question":"I am a big liver, A metal that is ductile can be pulled into this while cold & under pressure",
      "Answer":"wire",
      "Age":41
   },
   {
      "Category":"SCIENCE",
      "Question":"I am a big liver, In 1953 Watson & Crick built a model of the molecular structure of this, the gene-carrying substance",
      "Answer":"DNA",
      "Age":42
   },
   {
      "Category":"SCIENCE",
      "Question":"I am a big liver, Changes in the tropospheric layer of this are what gives us weather",
      "Answer":"the atmosphere",
      "Age":41
   },
   {
      "Category":"SCIENCE",
      "Question":"I am a big liver, In 70-degree air, a plane traveling at about 1,130 feet per second breaks it",
      "Answer":"Sound barrier",
      "Age":45
   }
]